[{"answer": "I wouldn't say they are angry.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "How are they going to find closure given they see such injustice here?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "No, I won't criticize the prosecution.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Do you think the prosecution dropped the ball in that regard and they should have had more people talking about the human being that Trayvon Martin was?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "I was not nearly as upset as many of the people in Boston are.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "What was your view of it?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well, first, this case was not about race at all and what happened, you have the race hustlers and poverty pimps like Jesse Jackson and Al Sharpton, and others who turned it into a race issue in order to gain power and wealth.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "What is your view about the verdict?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Well, George Zimmerman would have done whatever it took to protect himself.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "You really think George Zimmerman would have looked at a young white man in a hoodie and thought the same thing, that this guy is potential trouble?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, you know, there were pictures on his Facebook page of Trayvon Martin carrying -- having -- holding on to a gun, pot in front of him.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Everyone who smokes pot in America is a thug, are they?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Before they took his information off of his Facebook page, it was out there for everybody to see.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "I mean, you're saying everyone in America that has ever taken cannabis or ever been pictured with a gun is a thug, is that your -- is that your conclusion?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "He would -- he had been in trouble before.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Where was the evidence that he was a dangerous thug?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "You know, I think that Trayvon Martin at the end of the day was a 16-year-old kid.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "What do you think about all this?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "At least go through it with a fine-tooth comb and just make sure all the T's were crossed and all the I's were dotted because this is setting a terrible message -- it's sending out a terrible message to young teenagers.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "What would you like, if anything, for President Obama to do?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Well, I certainly disagree with -- respectfully to -- with Reverend Peterson.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "You see, I think this is -- Reverend Peterson.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "You guys -- you guys are hypocrites because if you truly cared about black Americans, why aren't you upset about the 500 homicides that took place in Chicago last year?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "You call us hypocrites.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "What am I not telling the truth about?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Yes, let me speak.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Reverend Peterson, will you -- will you let Raymond Santana speak?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Crime is crime regardless.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "ETERSON: Why don't you became aware on the black on black crime?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Trayvon -- he had a right to defend himself but nothing came out during the trial that George Zimmerman stalked Trayvon Martin, nor did he follow him after he was told not to, and that lie is being put out there in order to divide and conquer, as well, by keeping blacks and whites angry at one another.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Only George Zimmerman had the right to defend himself with a gun, right?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "But, Piers, why do his family --", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "How do you see a way through this?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "I said the same thing.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Where did you get this man from?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Trying to turn a thug into a hero.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Sir, can you be respectful?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "No, I don't think that race was the center.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Do you feel that race inevitably, as it did in the trial involving O.J. Simpson, that race was at the center of this trial?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Well, I guess that's the case in every trial, depending on who the jurors are.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "But as -- the point I was going to make, really, was that in your trial, for example, involving the death of your brother and others, having such a predominantly black jury, do you feel that the race element of that, of the jury selection led them to acquit somebody who many people believe should have been convicted because some people are saying in the Zimmerman trial that had you had more African-Americans on the jury than they would have related better perhaps to Trayvon Martin, to his background, to the star witness Rachel Jeantel, and you could perhaps have had a different verdict?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Do you ever get any sense of closure?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "And would you recommend that course of action to people who feel a sense of injustice?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I love it.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Has it brought you any satisfaction, perhaps a sense of karma that O.J. Simpson is currently incarcerated and maybe for a very long time for another offense?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I guess if I was ever in that situation, I'd be very happy for the self-defense law.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "What is your actual view about self-defense and Stand Your Ground and so on?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "I remember just, you know, us having fun and it was a little uncomfortable because there was so many people there.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "What is your memory of what happened?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Before actually my parents kind of taught me to be aware of my surroundings.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "And second, in that moment, what made you react the way that you did?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "But are you OK physically yourself now?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Was that part of your thinking when you said yes to his marriage proposal?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "Actually, Eugene chose it, not me so --", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Why did you choose, Kristin, the anniversary to get married?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Did he take a lot of weed?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "Like twice a week.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "How much would you say?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Twice a week?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130718pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Is that normal for teenagers in your community?", "qSentId": 616}]